We were gathered without any information on this day
What was announced was
The release of the second single of "Blue Sky I Wanted to See" on January 31 next year and the introduction of the selection system.
We also decided on the name of the selected members.
We will call it "Aozora Gumi".
The members who didn't make it into the Aozora group, we will name them as well.
The members who didn't make it, we will name them as well.
This team will be called Spider Team.
For the debut single, "Think about the Blue Sky," all 23 members were selected.
For the second single, the team was divided into two teams.
By dividing the team into two,
I believe that by dividing the team into two, we will be able to do a wider range of activities as a team.
In addition, by keeping the number of people in each team small, I would like to make it easier for people to remember our faces,
In addition, by keeping the number of members in each team small, I would like to make it easier for people to remember our faces.
Now, I would like to announce the members of the Aozora group.
First of all
Aoi Anno
Yuzu Ito
Ami Kanazawa
The 12 members selected for the Aozora-gumi are
Aozora-gumi will sing the title song of the second single
It was announced that they will be mainly active in the media, including singing the title song of the second single.
And the members of Spider group are
Hiroho Aoki, Rian Akita
Yuki Imai Riko Iwamoto
Ai Kinoshita, Miyuna Sunanaga, Koka Hagiwara, Hitomi Hasegawa, Mana Mochinaga, Miisa Yaegashi, and Yuyasu Yamaguchi.
I know it's frustrating in the sense that we weren't selected.
We will receive music for the Spider group, so please do your best for the Spider group's goals.
We would like to focus on individual real activities such as live performances.
I can't hide my upset at the announcement of the selection, which I am experiencing for the first time.
The members who were selected and those who were not selected had the same expressions on their faces.
There was a strange atmosphere here.
I had not imagined this development at all.
I thought we would be able to dance with 23 members again.
I thought we would be able to dance with 23 members again, so we were split into two groups, the blue sky group and the cloud group.
I still want to do my best with 23 members
There are many things we can do as 23 members.
I would like to be able to perform songs that people would like.
I hope to be able to perform more and more so that people can know more about "Boku wa
I know that this is to make Boku better known, but when the selection system was announced, it took time for some members to accept it.
It's frustrating, I mean, honestly, I guess I expected it.
With an announcement like this.
I had expected that I wouldn't be selected.
But when the announcement was made
I was convinced.
That's what I thought.
That's why I feel frustrated.
Of course I am very disappointed, but
But more than anything, I think it shows how good I am.
I think it's a direct reflection of my ability.
I have to accept that.
While some members were in tears with frustration
Riko Iwamoto stares at a single point.
It's frustrating, but it's more than frustration.
It's not that I'm frustrated.
I feel that I have to work harder.
Since I came here, I've only said I'm frustrated.
I thought there's no bottom.
I've decided to only look up.
When other people are working harder at dancing, I have to work harder.
I have to work harder at singing.
I have to work twice as hard as other people.
And Akita Liane, too.
But I still feel frustrated,
But when I think about it properly,
I'm still not at the level to be selected,
I am not yet at the level to be selected, in terms of dance and other technical skills,
When Nozaki made the announcement, he said that he was also thinking about popularity, so in that aspect as well, I'm still not there yet.
I'm still not there yet.
I don't know how to put it.
I can only accept it.
It's also frustrating that I'm the one who can accept it.
If I put it in a good way, I think there's still a lot of room for growth.
I think
I'm thinking about the future.
I'm just going to go for it.
I have no choice but to aim for the top.
I will not give up, and I will do my best.
The next day, a meeting was held with only the Spider group.
We talked about what we could do to help the members of the Spider group get to know each other.
The day after the announcement, the members talked about their honest thoughts and feelings.
There is a feeling of frustration.
but I also feel like there is nothing we can do better.
I also wonder if there is anything we can do better.
We are grateful for the opportunity to perform in Kumogumi alone,
I have to do my best in that environment,
I can't contribute anything unless I do my best in the environment I'm given.
I think I have no choice but to work hard here first.
We also exchanged opinions and discussed the future of the Spider group.
about the future of the Spider Team.
It's just too much work.
We should do a backflip or something.
We have strong personalities.
That's what we do.
Riko and I are the only ones who can do backflips.
Dance, lactice.
I'd like to be the only one who can do backflips with Riko.
I'd like to perform.
I'd like to work hard for our music
I would like to do my best
I would like to do my best for that.
With 11 members
The quality of the music is really good.
We used to have 23 members.
The reduced number of people means that it's easier for us to work together.
I think it's easier for each one of us to express our opinions, so I think it's better to have fewer people.
It doesn't matter if you're good at dancing or not.
I think it's easier to express your opinion.
Of course it's important to have lessons with the teacher, but I also want to have a lot of practice.
But we also want to have a lot of practice.
We want to have a lot of practice.
And if we feel something is not right, we can improve it.
And when we feel something is not right...
It's a little bit difficult to say.
It's a little hard to say.
But now that there are 11 of us, I think we can trust each other.
I wanted to have a relationship where I could say whatever I wanted to say.
It's because there are so few of us, after all.
Like, I have feelings for you, or I'm going to be more of a master.
Sure, it's a little hard to say how many of us are a little bit at a time. I have to go around a few times,
Because there are so few of us, we seem to be able to bond, so it's not easy to express our opinions.
From Hitomi Hasegawa's idea, we, the 11 members of the spider group, decided to support each other and do our best.
As we all discussed, we will teach each other lessons.
Let's do our best!
Oh! ImaYuki was in charge of the narration this time!
We have been feeling tight since the day of the selection announcement.
From now on, the 11 of us will do our best while supporting each other.
I hope you will pay attention to Komogumi as well!
Please look forward to the next episode! Thank you for watching!